Rock, we uh kind of talked about it
there at the end of the season, just the
five teams in five years and the the
grind that you know puts on you to have
some some stability here. You know, what
what does that mean to you?
>> Uh it's not so much about that. I think
it's more just wanting to be back here.
You know, I feel like um honestly
whenever I uh ended the season, I was I
was ready to go usually, you know, um
from those four or five teams I had been
on. Like when it was time to go, I was
happy to go. But um this was the first
time I really wanted to come back and um
I let my agent know that from the from
like before the season had ended, I
already let him know I wanted to come
back. So I'm just glad to be back.
>> Why did you want to come back here? just
the the culture, the locker room, um
like what it means to be a Lion, you
know, what it's all about here. Like I
feel like that's like something I can
get behind, something that I, you know,
I could I really mesh well with.
>> No disrespect to those other teams, but
why do you think that this stood out
versus those other?
>> It's a better fit. Like, you know,
everybody's different. Um, every
organization is different. Each player
is different, coaches, staffs, all of is
different. And like certain guys, you
know, fit better with certain teams. And
I feel like I fit better here than I fit
with those previous four, three or four
teams or whatever.
>> Maybe it was when the the pads came on
and we got to see the real you, but it
was pretty clear like the fit, you know,
personality, culture, style, skill. When
did when did you recognize like you
belonged here? You know, how how long
after you initially signed? Honestly,
before that, like the reputation around
the league is like, you know, the Lions
have a certain reputation about, you
know, being gritty, being tough, working
hard, you know, like winning games, you
know, being physical, all that good
stuff. And, um, like I've I looked at
myself as that kind of a player. Like I
like being physical. I like being tough.
I like doing the work. I like, you know,
like I like I like doing things the
right way. So, um, you know, I I I I
thought that I would fit well here, but
then coming in OTAAS, getting around the
guys, you know, then through training
camp, seeing like, okay, this is
definitely a place that I want to
definitely want to be.
>> Do you know Go ahead.
>> I as off the field, like I mean, I know
we talked last year about how you kind
of find a home here. How much did that
play into the decision to maybe come
back as well?
>> A lot. A lot. This um this place is
special, man. um the community like the
locker room inside of the building is
special, but outside of the building is
actually really really special to me. We
have some like some really like really
good friends and really, you know, I'm
really um uh really embedded into this
community here in this um in this city.
So like I'm I'm thankful to be here.
>> Rock, do you know Roger McCreary at all?
Like do do you know about his his game?
Do you know him personally? What do you
think he might be able to add to your
guys defense?
>> Yeah, I know. I know. I knew I played
against him when he was in Tennessee.
He's a really good, you know, slot. He
plays inside, plays outside slot and
outside. Um, he's a good player. Came
out of Auburn, you know, tenacious. I
think he's a physical guy. He covers
well. I think he does a lot of things
really well. So, I'm excited to play
with the guy.
>> You, um, dipped your toe in safety last
year. Uh,
>> it was, uh, it was an interesting
transition. I'm just curious. Um, how
much do you think that, you know,
there's still possibility or or room to
grow and and expand the versatility
there? I definitely think I can grow
there and expand there. Um, will I be
put there? I don't know. I'm just, you
know, like whatever these coaches ask me
to do, I'm going to do. If it's corner,
safety, special teams, whatever it is.
But, um, I think I definitely can play
back there. Definitely.
>> You feel like that's something that's
still on the table for you? I don't know
if you guys have discussed that with the
coaches yet, but could that be part of
your role next season?
>> I'm not sure. I haven't discussed it
with them, you know, yet, but um, if it
is, I'm excited for it. If not, is what
it is. Whatever it is, like whether if
I'm playing corner, safety, if I'm
playing slot, if I'm playing special
teams, whatever it is, I'm just here to
do my job, you know, do my part, my one
of 11.
>> What did you like about playing safety
in those reps that you got in camp?
>> Just different, man. It's just something
different, you know? Um, a different
perspective of the game, like you have
to widen your lens, more communication.
Um, it's just different. It's a new
challenge, you know? So, I'm always up
for a challenge. So, it was it was
something cool. I liked it.
What are you most proud of or or happy
about the way you performed last season?
And and what do you kind of want to
clean up or or be a better version of
yourself this upcoming season?
>> I want to take the ball away more this
year. I really want to take the ball
away. I thought I um I really thought
that I left some on the on the field
last year. Um some interceptions, some
forced fumbles. Um I want to do a better
job of that this year. I want to take
the ball away. And then um last year I
think I you know I was I was proud of
the way that I stepped up when I got
opportunity. Um I got to do a lot of
cool things last year. Match match a lot
of really good receivers um and do
things in my career that I haven't done
that up to that point I had I hadn't
done yet. So I thought that was really
cool. Follow guys around. Um and um that
was really cool stepping up when guys
got hurt and like not taking a step back
or not missing a beat. Just just roll
it, you know. Um I was proud of that.
But definitely this year I want to take
the ball away. Definitely.
>> Do you did your perspective of yourself
change at all through those experiences
of going out and and doing those things
that you thought you might be able to?
>> I always believe that I could do that.
Like I always I always like
wholeheartedly believe I could do that,
you know. Um sometimes it didn't work
out that way early in my career or I
didn't get the opportunity or if I did
get the opportunity it just didn't work,
you know, for whatever reason. But um I
knew I believed in myself that I could
definitely go out there and do that. So
I'm like happy with with that.
>> Rock, this defense was playing pretty
well last year in the first half of the
year before the injuries kind of piled
up in the secondary. Have you thought
about or have you guys talked about
amongst each other what you guys might
be capable of next year if that
secondary can can get and stay healthy?
>> Yeah, definitely. I mean, um, throughout
the season, we talked about it. Um,
getting getting guys healthy and getting
back to like our full strength or
whatever and get our all all the guys
back healthy. Um, and even after later
in the season, we talked about it. Um,
we just excited, man. Just excited to
get everybody back. Excited to get out
there and play together as one, you
know, make plays on the ball, turn the
ball over, win a lot of games. That's
what that's what we're trying to do.
>> Well, we have you um, you know, and Rick
Shaw is a young player who's dealt with
injuries. I was just curious, did you
have any conversations with him either
during the season or this off
seasonason? I guess where do you think
his head's at?
>> Yeah, me and me and pretty cool, man.
Like I like And this is a really
talented young player. Um, I like that
guy. Like he has a right mindset and
mentality. I think he's going to be a
great player in this league for a long
time. I think he going to be he's going
to play until he doesn't want to play
anymore, 10, 12, 15 years, whatever it
is. Um, I think he has a really bright
future. I always tell him that like you
have a really bright future. All you got
to do is just get healthy. Once he gets
healthy, the sky's is the limit for that
guy. So, I'm excited to see him do
things this year and then the rest of
his career as well.
>> Hey, was was playing under Townsen part
of the appeal for you of coming back
here? And I guess what did you
appreciate about being in this room last
year?
>> Shay's a guy, man. He played in the NFL
for a really long time. So, he has a
different perspective than a lot of
coaches cuz he's actually done it
before. So, when you're talking to him
and you're telling him something, he's
like he knows exactly how that feels to
be in that position. So he can coach you
in a from a different perspective than a
lot of coaches can cuz a lot of them
haven't done it at a high level that
he's done it like for so many years. So
it's really cool having having him as a
coach. He's a really he's a good guy,
you know. That's the thing I like about
this staff. It's some really good men on
on on that staff, men and women on that
staff.
>> Okay. Thank you.
[music]
Hey, hey, hey.